<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-11-19T13:53:58-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">NYC 25x25</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2021/11/16/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2021-11-16T16:33:59-05:00</published><updated>2021-11-16T16:33:59-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2021/11/16/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2021/11/16/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll requires blog post files to be named according to the following format:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YEAR-MONTH-DAY-title.MARKUP&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Where &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YEAR&lt;/code&gt; is a four-digit number, &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;MONTH&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;DAY&lt;/code&gt; are both two-digit numbers, and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;MARKUP&lt;/code&gt; is the file extension representing the format used in the file. After that, include the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated. Jekyll requires blog post files to be named according to the following format: YEAR-MONTH-DAY-title.MARKUP Where YEAR is a four-digit number, MONTH and DAY are both two-digit numbers, and MARKUP is the file extension representing the format used in the file. After that, include the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works. Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets: def print_hi(name) puts &quot;Hi, #{name}&quot; end print_hi('Tom') #=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT. Check out the Jekyll docs for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at Jekyll’s GitHub repo. If you have questions, you can ask them on Jekyll Talk.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to my new site!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/technology/2020/09/14/testing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to my new site!" /><published>2020-09-14T07:37:43-04:00</published><updated>2020-09-14T07:37:43-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/technology/2020/09/14/testing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/technology/2020/09/14/testing.html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;is-this-thing-on&quot;&gt;Is this thing on?&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/engineering-education/assets/images/welcome/new-site.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;demo image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="technology" /><summary type="html">Is this thing on?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Challenge</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/report" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Challenge" /><published>2020-09-14T07:37:43-04:00</published><updated>2020-09-14T07:37:43-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/testing</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/report">&lt;h2 id=&quot;nyc-25x25-a-challenge-to-new-york-citys-next-leaders-to-give-streets-back-to-people&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;NYC 25x25&lt;/em&gt;: A CHALLENGE TO NEW YORK CITY’S NEXT LEADERS TO GIVE STREETS BACK TO PEOPLE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taken together, streets and sidewalks are New York City’s largest publicly owned space. Cars dominate that space. Despite the spatial abundance of 6,300 miles of asphalt and three million free parking spaces, New Yorkers’ everyday lives are relegated to narrow sidewalks and the margins of streets, where we are left to fight over the precious remaining scraps of our public space.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past two decades, elected officials have made little citywide progress in upending this wholesale car dominance — opting for disconnected and piecemeal improvements that fail to effectively manage our streets as a system of public spaces. For New Yorkers, the negative effects of a car-filled city remain. Asthma, heart disease, and preterm births rise with car pollution. Carbon emissions remain high and climate change threatens our future. New Yorkers risk life-altering injury and death crossing the street. Bus riders waste time on gridlocked streets. Burdensome commutes and a lack of transportation choices isolate communities from opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With a coalition of more than 80 unions, and economic, educational, environmental, disability rights, and public health organizations, Transportation Alternatives challenges New York City’s next leaders to end this vicious cycle by making a specific and substantial promise: to convert 25 percent of car space into space for people by 2025.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, New York City faces a budget shortfall, a crisis of racial injustice, rising inequality and traffic violence, the loss of millions of jobs and small businesses, and the ongoing threat of climate change. Our recovery can begin, in part, by reimagining our largest public asset — New York City’s 6,300 miles of streets and three million free parking spaces — in support of the needs of all New Yorkers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;./assets/images/home/25.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image info&quot; /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;WXY&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today, New York City faces a budget shortfall, a crisis of racial injustice, rising inequality and traffic violence, the loss of millions of jobs and small businesses, and the ongoing threat of climate change. Our recovery can begin, in part, by reimagining our largest public asset — New York City’s 6,300 miles of streets and three million free parking spaces — in support of the needs of all New Yorkers.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="technology" /><summary type="html">NYC 25x25: A CHALLENGE TO NEW YORK CITY’S NEXT LEADERS TO GIVE STREETS BACK TO PEOPLE</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What we can build</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/build" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What we can build" /><published>2020-09-14T07:37:43-04:00</published><updated>2020-09-14T07:37:43-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/build</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/build">&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-we-can-build-the-spatial-potential-of-city-streets&quot;&gt;WHAT WE CAN BUILD: THE SPATIAL POTENTIAL OF CITY STREETS&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One hundred years ago, New York City streets underwent a paradigm shift. At the time, and for decades prior, city streets were open-air marketplaces and social spaces, and avenues were built for strolling and later, a place to catch an above-ground public transit line. But that all changed as the automobile became affordable to more Americans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cars and people briefly competed for streets. Cars won, and our city has suffered every day since. Countless small businesses were closed or relegated indoors, children were taught to stay out of the street, above-ground transit lines were dismantled, sidewalks were narrowed so streets could be widened, highways destroyed neighborhoods, car owners were saddled with crippling debt, traffic injuries and fatalities became everyday tragedies, and poor, immigrant, and Black communities bore the brunt of these changes. Car traffic took over the majority of New York City’s public space.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">WHAT WE CAN BUILD: THE SPATIAL POTENTIAL OF CITY STREETS</summary></entry></feed>